nickels-n-dimes.com 2012-12-31

# Disclosure / Privacy Policy Nickels-n-Dimes Nickels-n-Dimes | Save Money | Free Kindle Books | Coupons | Magazine Deals | Grocery Store Deals | Free Christian Fiction Books

### DISCLOSURE POLICY

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact  [Lisa Thompson of Nickels-n-Dimes](mailto:lisa\(@\)nickels-n-dimes\(.\)com).

My goal at at Nickels-n-Dimes.com is to help you save your hard earned nickels-n-dimes.  I regularly share great coupons, great deals I find, products I like, and I also share some of our journey of getting out of debt.

AI spend a huge amount of time and energy on this blog and as such, I feel it is permissible to be compensated. I accept advertising and participate in various affiliate programs which provide some income for my family.

Although I share deals on products that I don’t use, if I recommend a product, it is only because I use this product personally or have seen first hand what a great product it is.

Integrity is important to me and I will do my best to earn and keep your trust.

And here’s the additional legal jargon just to make sure things are covered:

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, paid travel, free products or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to [http://www.disclosurepolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/) -  This policy is valid from 25 October 2009

### 

### PRIVACY POLICY

**Nickels-n-Dimes respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Nickels-n-Dimes.

**Credit card details**

Nickels-n-Dimes will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Nickels-n-Dimes.

**External Sites.**

Nickels-n-Dimes is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Nickels-n-Dimes to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Nickels-n-Dimes does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Nickels-n-Dimes and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Nickels-n-Dimes have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster.](mailto:lisa\(@\)nickels-n-dimes\(.\)com)

_If you enjoyed this post, make sure you subscribe to my[RSS feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/nnd)!!_

_© 2008-2012, Nickels-n-Dimes. All rights reserved._

_This post may contain affiliate links. Please see our full_[ _disclosure policy_](http://blog.nickels-n-dimes.com/about-2/disclosure-privacy-policy/) _for more information._
